// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Dimensional formula for angular momemntum is?",
    answer: "ml²T–¹",
    options: [
      "ml²T–¹",
      "ml³T–¹",
      "mlT–¹",
      "ml³T–¹"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "the quentity represented by (mass*pressure)/density?",
    answer: "work",
    options: [
      "power",
      "force",
      "work",
      "impulse"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "The angle between i+j and j+k is ?",
    answer: "60°",
    options: [
      "0°",
      "90°",
      "45°",
      "60°",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "The angle between A+B and A-B is ?",
    answer: "between  0° and 180°",
    options: [
      "always 0°",
      "always 90°",
      "always 180°",
      "between 0° and 180°"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Two bodys are dropped from the same point after an inter of is it acceleration due to gravity 10m/s^2 there seperation 4s after the release of the ball will be",
    answer: "35m",
    options: [
      "50m",
      "5m",
      "25m",
      "35m"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "The velocity of a particle of is given by v=5-t^2m/s.The average acceleration of particle between 3 and 5 sec will be ?",
    answer: "-8m/s²",
    options: [
      "2m/s²",
      "-8m/s²",
      "-14m/s²",
      "9m/s²"
    ]
  }, {
    numb: 7,
    question: "In the equation of  motion of a body is given by S=8t²-8t³, it is moving with?",
    answer: "variable retardation",
    options: [
      "uniform velcity",
      "uniform acceleration",
      "variable acceleration",
      "variable retardation"
    ]
  },
   {
    numb: 8,
    question: "A football player kick a ball at angle of 60^ with the vertical with a vleocity at 60m/s the maximum height reached by the ball is?",
    answer: "45m",
    options: [
      "45m",
      "31m",
      "2.25m",
      "0.225m"
    ]
  },
   {
    numb: 9,
    question: "The maximum range of a given on horizontal terrain is 16km the nuzzle velocity of the shell (g=10/ms)",
    answer: "400m/s",
    options: [
      "200m/s",
      "256m/s",
      "400m/s",
      "800m/s"
    ]
  }, {
    numb: 10,
    question: "The displacement is given by x=2t+t+5 the acceleration at t=2sec is:?",
    answer: "4m/s²",
    options: [
      "4m/s²",
      "8m/s²",
      "10m/s²",
      "15m/s²"
    ]
  }, 
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "Displacement 'x' of a simple Harmonte. oscillator Varies with time according to the differential equation {dx}{dt}+4x=0 Then its time period is?",
    answer: "π sec",
    options: [
      "π/2 sec",
      "π sec",
      "2π sec",
      "4π sec"
    ]
  }, 
  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "The displacement of a simple oscillator is given by 4=4~cos(2\pi t+\pi(4). Then velocity of the oscillator att=2see PS",
    answer: "4√2 πms–¹",
    options: [
      "4√2 πms–¹",
      "4π/√2ms–¹",
      "√2π/4ms–¹",
      "4√2/πms–¹"
    ]
  },
   {
    numb: 13,
    question: "Velocity of a simple Harmonie oscillation is given by v=√144-16xms–¹ where x is displacement in metre. Then Maximum Velocity of that oscillator is?",
    answer: "12ms–¹",
    options: [
      "6ms–¹",
      "12ms–¹",
      "16ms–¹",
      "8ms–¹"
    ]
  }, 
  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "The threshold of hearing is 10–¹²wm–2 Its value in dbis?",
    answer: "0",
    options: [
      "0",
      "1",
      "0.5",
      "None"
    ]
  }, 
  {
    numb: 15,
    question: "The velocity of sound in agasin which two waves of wavelengths lm an d1.01 m Produce 10 beats in 3 second is?",
    answer: "336.7ms–¹",
    options: [
      "336.7ms–¹",
      "337.6ms–¹",
      "363.7ms–¹",
      "333.3ms–¹"
    ]
  }, 
  {
    numb: 16,
    question: "100 cc of air care measured at 200 If the temperature be raised to 50°c, what will be the Volume, Pressure remaining constant ?",
    answer: "110.24cc",
    options: [
      "110.24cc",
      "124.26cc",
      "156.29cc",
      "29.9cc"
    ]
  }, 
  {
    numb: 17,
    question: "A given Mars of a gas exerts of pressure of 72cm of mercury at 27c. It is heated at constant volume and the pressure. was found to be 90cm of mercury. what is the final Temparature?",
    answer: "102°c",
    options: [
      "108°c",
      "102°c",
      "189°c",
      "100°c"
    ]
  }, 
  {
    numb: 18,
    question: "Boyle's law holds good for an ideal gas during?",
    answer: "Iothermal changes",
    options: [
      "isobaric changes",
      "Iothermal changes",
      "Isochoric changes",
      "esotropic changes"
    ]
  }, 
  {
    numb: 19,
    question: "An ideal gas is allowed to expand freely against Vaccum in a rigid insulated?",
    answer: "inerease in internal energy",
    options: [
      "inerease in internal energy",
      "Increase in Temparatore",
      "decrease in Internal energy but increase  in Temparatore.",
      "None of there"
    ]
  }, 
  {
    numb: 20,
    question: "The threshold wavelength is 2000°. The work function is?",
    answer: "6-2 ev",
    options: [
      "16.25ev",
      "6-2 ev",
      "6.2Mer",
      "6.3Ker"
    ]
  },
];